<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<dcd sitecode="POU">

<ad id="3564456">
  <start-date>2014-03-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-02</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    ADVERTISEMENT FOR BIDS  Hyde Park Water Treatment Facility  Treated Water Building Roof Replacement     RECEIPT OF BIDS:  Sealed Bids on forms prepared by the OWNER will be received by the Dutchess County Water and Wastewater Au- thority until 11 AM (l- ocal time) Tuesday, April 1, 2014 for the fol- lowing contract:  Construction Contract HPW-PWC-2014-01 Re- placement of Treated Water Building Roof  All submissions shall be in accordance with the Information for Bidders, Drawings, and Specifi- cations prepared by the Owner.  Bids will be publicly opened and read aloud at 11 AM (local time) Tuesday, April 1, 2014 at the offices of the Dut- chess County Water and Wastewater Au- thority, 27 High Street, Poughkeepsie, New York 845-486-3601.  Bids will be reviewed and the Contract will be awarded within one hundred five (105) days of receipt of bids.   Dutchess County Water and Wastewater Au- thority and the contrac- tors it retains are sub- ject to the provisions of Articles 5-A of the Gen- eral Municipal Law (pu- blic contracts); Labor Law Article 220 (prevai- ling wage rate); and Ex- ecutive Law Article 15 and Labor Law Section 220-e (Equal Opportuni- ty in Employment).  All employees and appli- cants for employment shall be afforded equal opportunity without discrimination. Successful Bidder will be required to submit a staffing plan to assure attainment of minority and women employ- ment goals.  NATURE OF PROJECT:  The removal of existing roof hatches, flashings, expansion joints, cop- ings, built up roofs and insulation to concrete roof deck; installation of new roof hatches; application of moisture barrier to the existing deck; and installation of roof insulation and roofing system, flash- ings, expansion joints and copings. Contractor will be re- sponsible for removal and maintaining contin- uity of lightning protec- tion system to facilitate roofing, flashing and coping removal and re- placement and reinstal- lation of any displaced or damaged lightning protection components.   VIEWING OF DOCU- MENTS:  The Information for Bid- ders, Drawings, and Specifications may be reviewed at the follow- ing locations:  1.Dutchess County Wa- ter & Wastewater Au- thority, 27 High Street, Poughkeepsie, NY 12601  (Phone 845-486-3601)  OBTAINING DOCU- MENTS:  The Contract Docu- ments may be obtained only from the Authority upon payment of a $50.00 nonrefundable fee per set.  The fee shall be in certified check, exact cash, or money order and be made payable to the Dutchess County Water and Wastewater Au- thority.  MANDATORY PREBID MEETING:  The Owner will conduct a mandatory, pre-bid meeting on Wednesday, March 19, 2014 at 10:00 AM local time at the Au- thority's Offices at 27 High Street, Pough- keepsie, NY 12601.  All bidders desiring to re- spond to this solicita- tion must attend this meeting.  Failure to at- tend this meeting and sign attendance roster will be basis to return any bid to a bidder not documented in atten- dance.  BIDDERS QUALIFICA- TION STATEMENT:  Bidders attention is called to Bidder's Qual- ification Statement in- cluded with the Bidding Documents.  Failure to submit completed Bid- der's Qualification Statement with the Bid is basis for Bid being determined as non-res- ponsive.  OWNERS RIGHTS RE- SERVED:  The Dutchess County Water & Wastewater Authority, hereinafter called the OWNER, re- serves the right to re- ject any or all Bids and to waive any formality or technicality in any Bid in the interest of the OWNER.  STATEMENT OF NON- COLLUSION:  Bidders on the Con- tracts are required to execute a non-collusion bidding certificate pur- suant to Section 103d of the General Municipal Law of the State of New York.  OWNER'S BOARD AND EMPLOYEE CONDUCT:  Bidders' attention is called to Instruction to Bidders Section titled Owner's Board Member and Employee Conduct in regards to Owner's policy in regards to gifts and remuneration to its employees.   NYS PREVAILING WAGE RATES:  Bidders' attention is called that the project work falls under the NYS Public Work Pre- vailing Wage and Supplement determin- ation which is included in the project docu- ments.  NYS DOL INELIGIBLE TO BID EMPLOYERS:  Bidders' attention is called to the list of em- ployers ineligible to bid or be awarded any pub- lic work contract which is included in the pro- ject documents.  OSHA 10 HOUR SAFETY TRAINING COMPLIAN- CE:  Owner requires that all supervision, laborers, workers and mechanics working on site be cer- tified as successfully completing the USA De- partment of Labor OSHA 10-hour construc- tion safety and health course.&ldquo;  WICK'S LAW SUBCON- TRACTING INFORMA- TION:  Bidder's attention is called to the require- ments of the Wick's Law that requires the submission of the name and contract amount for Electrical, Plumbing and HVAC work includ- ed in the Bidder's bid amount and the method of reporting such names and amounts with the Contractor's bid for contracts up to $500,000 in value.  EQUAL OPPORTUNI- TY/AFFIRMATIVE AC- TION:  The OWNER hereby no- tifies all Bidders that it will affirmatively insure that in regard to any Agreement entered into pursuant to this adver- tisement, all employees and applicants for em- ployment shall be af- forded equal opportuni- ty without discrimina- tion.  Successful Bidder will be required to sub- mit a staffing plan. Successful bidder will be required to submit a Minority/Women Busi- ness Enterprise Plan to assure attainment of Minority/Women Busi- ness Enterprise goals.  BY ORDER OF THE DUTCHESS COUNTY WATER & WASTEWA- TER AUTHORITY  AN EQUAL OPPORTUNI- TY/AFFIRMATIVE AC- TION EMPLOYER                                  4456
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563335">
  <start-date>2014-02-25</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-02</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    LEGAL NOTICE    NOTICE is hereby given that a license, number &ldquo;Pending&ldquo; for Beer, Wine and Liquor has been applied for by the undersigned to sell Beer, Wine and Liquor at retail in a restaurant under the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law at 3997 ROUTE 22 SUITE B WASSAIC NY 12592 for On Premises Con- sumption.         THE DUGOUT DDL LLC  THE DUGOUT SPORTS BAR & GRILL  3997 ROUTE 22  SUITE B  WASSAIC NY 12592                                    3335
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563336">
  <start-date>2014-02-25</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-02</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    LEGAL NOTICE    NOTICE is hereby given that a license, number &ldquo;Pending&ldquo; for Beer, Wine and Liquor has been applied for by the undersigned to sell Beer, Wine and Liquor at retail in a restaurant under the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law at 418-420 MAIN STREET BEACON NY 12508 for On Premises Consumption.         ELLA'S BELLAS BAK- ERY, LLC  ELLA'S BELLAS  418-420 MAIN STREET  BEACON NY 12508                                    3336
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562221">
  <start-date>2014-03-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-09</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    NOTICE CONCERNING THE EXAMINATION OF ASSESSMENT INVENTO- RY AND VALUATION DA- TA  (Pursuant to Section 501 of the Real Property Tax Law)     NOTICE is hereby given that the City of Bea- con's Assessment Inventory and Valuation Data is available for ex- amination and review.   This data is the infor- mation that will be used to establish the asses- sment of each parcel which will appear on the Tentative Asses- sment Roll of the City of Beacon which will be filed on or before May 1, 2014.   The information may be reviewed by appoint- ment in the Assessor's office at:   City of Beacon  One Municipal Plaza  Beacon, New York 12508   On May 2, 2014 between the hours of 12:00 p.m. and 4:00 p.m.  AND  On May 9, 2014 be- tween the hours of 12:00 p.m. and 4:00 p.m.    To set up an appoint- ment to review the as- sessment information please call the City As- sessor's Office at 845- 838-5025      Kathy S. Martin   Assessor   City of Beacon  DATED: February 18, 2013   PUBLISH:  March 3, 2013 and March 10, 2013                                     2221
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563506">
  <start-date>2014-03-01</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-02</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    NOTICE CONCERNING THE EXAMINATION OF ASSESSMENT INVENTO- RY AND VALUATION DATA (Pursuant to Section 501 of the Real Property Tax Law) Notice is Hereby Given that Assessment Inven- tory  and Valuation Data is Available for Ex- amination and Review. This Data is the Infor- mation which will be used to establish tthe Assessment of Each Parcel which will ap- pear on the Tentative Assessment Roll of the City of Poughkeepsie which will be filed on or before May 1, 2014. This is not the new 2014 tax assessments but rather the information that will be used to es- tablish the 2014 tax roll. The information  may be reviewed, by ap- pointment, in the City of Poughkeepsie, NY 12601 on the following dates and times. On March 11th, 2014 from 9am to 4pm and on March 18, 2014 from 9am to 4pm. To set up an appoint- ment to review these records, please call the City of Poughkeepsie's Assessors office at 845- 451-4039.  Dated: February 14, 2014  John Taylor Assessor                                    3506
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564369">
  <start-date>2014-02-28</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-02</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    Notice is hereby given that a license, Serial Number 2194482, for beer, liquor and wine has been applied for by the undersigned, Red Brick Lounge, Inc. d/b/a Princess, to sell beer, li- quor and wine at retail in a restaurant under the Alcoholic Beverage Control Law at 230-234 Salt Point Turnpike, Town of Poughkeepsie, County of Dutchess and State of New York for on premises consump- tion.  Red Brick Lounge, Inc. d/b/a Princess                                    4369
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564382">
  <start-date>2014-03-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-23</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    NOTICE OF SALE SU- PREME COURT COUNTY OF DUTCHESS JPMor- gan Chase Bank, NA, Plaintiff, against Nan- cey E. Walker; Marc I. Platt; et al., De- fendant(s). Pursuant to a Judgment of Foreclo- sure and Sale duly dat- ed January 10, 2014 I, the undersigned Refer- ee will sell at public auction  in the Dutchess County Courthouse, 10 Market Street, Pough- keepsie, New York on March 31, 2014 at 9:30AM, premises known as 28 Regency Drive, Poughkeepsie, NY 12603. All that cer- tain plot piece or parcel of land, with the build- ings and improvements erected, situate, lying and being in the Town of Poughkeepsie, Coun- ty of Dutchess and State of NY, Section 6262 Block 02 Lot 911804.  Approximate amount of judgment $426,957.01 plus inter- est and costs.  Premises will be sold subject to provisions of filed Judgment Index# 2010- 397. David D. Hagstrom, Esq., Referee Shapiro, DiCaro & Barak, LLC At- torney(s) for the Plain- tiff 250 Mile Crossing Boulevard, Suite One, Rochester, NY 14624 (877) 759-1835 Dated: February 25, 2014 1084379 3/3, 3/10, 3/17, 03/24/2014                                     4382
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3561969">
  <start-date>2014-02-24</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-16</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    NOTICE OF SALE SU- PREME COURT COUNTY OF DUTCHESS JPMor- gan Chase Bank, Na- tional Association, Plaintiff, against Robert A. Bundy a/k/a Robert Bundy, Defendant(s). Pursuant to a Judgment of Foreclosure and Sale duly dated January 9, 2014 I, the undersigned Referee will sell at pub- lic auction  in the Dut- chess County Court- house, 10 Market Street, Poughkeepsie, New York on March 24, 2014 at 10:00AM, prem- ises known as 296 Ket- chamtown Road, Wap- pingers Falls, NY 12590. All that certain plot piece or parcel of land, with the buildings and improvements erected, situate, lying and being in the Town of Wap- pinger, County of Dut- chess and State of NY, Section: 6156 Block: 02 Lot: 570840. Approximate amount of judgment $249,232.43 plus interest and costs. Premises will be sold subject to provisions of filed Judgment Index# 2013-515. Samuel P. Brooke, Esq., Referee Shapiro, DiCaro & Bar- ak, LLC Attorney(s) for the Plaintiff 250 Mile Crossing Boulevard, Suite One, Rochester, NY 14624 (877) 759-1835 Dated: February 12, 2014 1082516 2/24, 3/3, 3/10, 03/17/2014                                     1969
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562154">
  <start-date>2014-02-24</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-16</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    NOTICE OF SALE SU- PREME COURT COUNTY OF DUTCHESS JPMor- gan Chase Bank, Na- tional Association, Plaintiff, against Philip J. Mallozzi a/k/a Philip Mallozzi; Susan Malloz- zi; et al., Defendant(s). Pursuant to a Judgment of Foreclosure and Sale duly dated December 17, 2013 I, the under- signed Referee will sell at public auction  at the Dutchess County Court- house, rear vestibule, 10 Market Street, Poughkeepsie, New York on March 24, 2014 at 9:30AM, premises known as 70 Van Wyck Lake Road, Fishkill, NY 12524. All that certain plot piece or parcel of land, with the buildings and improvements erected, situate, lying and being in the Town of Fishkill, County of Dutchess and State of NY, Section 6255 Block 00 Lot 311431. Approximate amount of judgment $331,136.22 plus interest and costs. Premises will be sold subject to provisions of filed Judgment Index# 2012-4467. Sharon M. Faulkner, Esq., Referee Shapiro, DiCaro & Bar- ak, LLC Attorney(s) for the Plaintiff 250 Mile Crossing Boulevard, Suite One, Rochester, NY 14624 (877) 759-1835 Dated: February 14, 2014 1083079 2/24, 3/3, 3/10, 03/17/2014                                     2154
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3561973">
  <start-date>2014-02-24</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-16</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    NOTICE OF SALE  SUPREME COURT: DUT- CHESS COUNTY  RBS Citizens, N.A.; Plaintiff(s)  vs. MICHAEL G THOMP- SON; et al; Defendant(s)  Attorney (s) for Plaintiff (s): ROSICKI, ROSICKI & ASSOCIATES, P.C., 2 Summit Court, Suite 301, Fishkill, New York, 12524, 845.897.1600  Pursuant to judgment of foreclosure and sale granted herein on or about May 1, 2013, I will sell at Public Auction to the highest bidder at the Supreme Court (Du- tchess) 10 Market Street, Poughkeepsie, NY.  On March 25, 2014 at 10:00 AM  Premises known as 2 South Avenue, Pleasant Valley, NY 12569  Section: 6363 Block: 04 Lot: 849399  ALL that certain plot, piece or parcel of land, with the buildings and improvements thereon erected, situate, lying and being in the Town of Pleasant Valley, Dut- chess County, New Yor- k.  As more particularly de- scribed in the judgment of foreclosure and sale.  Sold subject to all of the terms and conditions contained in said judgment and terms of sale.  Approximate amount of judgment $109,702.37 plus interest and costs.  INDEX NO. 2012-3750  Patricia A. Cocchia, Esq., REFEREE                                     1973
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563450">
  <start-date>2014-03-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-18</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    NOTICE OF SALE   SUPREME COURT OF THE STATE OF NEW YORK  COUNTY OF DUTCHESS  &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;- &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;- &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;X  CLAPP HILL, LLC,    Plaintiff,    -against-    RAYMOND PATIERNO; ANTHONY VALENTINO;  LARRY THEW, Individu- ally; JOHN THEW, Indi- vidually;  LARRY THEW and JOHN THEW, as Trustees of the  GERALD THEW FAMILY TRUST; LARRY THEW and  JOHN THEW, as Trust- ees of the R.W. THEW TRUST;  PEOPLE OF THE STATE OF NEW YORK by New York  State Tax Commission; UNITED STATES OF AMERICA, by  and through the Com- missioner of the Inter- nal Revenue Service;  JOHN DOE and JANE DOE being fictitious names, it being  the intention of Plaintiff to designate any and all persona or  parties in possession of or having an interest in the premisesIndex #: 2011-3719  other than named De- fendants,   Defendants.  &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;- &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;- &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;X  In pursuance and by vir- tue of a Judgment of Foreclosure and Sale dated November 4, 2013, duly granted by this Court and entered in the Dutchess County Clerk's Office on the 12th day of December 2013 and pursuant to a Stipulation and Order of Substitution of Plaintiff and for Judgment of Foreclosure dated No- vember 4, 2013 and en- tered in the Dutchess County Clerk's Office on December 12, 2013I, the undersigned referee, duly appointed in this action for such purpose, will offer for sale and sell at public auction to the highest bidder, at the Dutchess County Courthouse, 1st Floor, rear vestibule, 10 Mar- ket Street, Poughkeep- sie, New York 12601 on the 26th day of March 2014 at 10:30 o'clock in the forenoon of that day, the mortgaged premises directed in and by said judgment to be sold and in said judgment described as follows:   ALL that certain plot, piece or parcel of land identified as follows:  in the Town of Beekman, New York, a parcel to- taling approximately 128.1 acres bearing Grid Nos. 6559-00-018292; in the Town of Beekman and the Town of La- Grange, New York, two parcels of approxi- mately 47.43 acres and approximately 7.94 acres conveyed by deed on or about October 6, 2006 and recorded in the Dutchess County Clerk's Office in deed book 22006 at page 8451; in the Town of Beekman, New York, a parcel totaling approxi- mately 8.5 acres bear- ing Grid No. 6559-00- 988522-00; in the Town of LaGrange, New York a parcel totaling ap- proximately 2.2 acres bearing Grid No. 6559- 04-597475; in the Town of LaGrange, New York a parcel totaling ap- proximately .58 acres bearing Grid No. 6559- 04-544442; and in the Town of Beekman, New York a parcel of about 6.9 acres bearing Grid No. 6559-00-993170, all of which properties are more particularly de- scribed in the Exhibit &ldquo;1&ldquo;  attached to the afo- resaid judgment of fore- closure on file in the Of- fice of the Clerk of the County of Dutchess.   Lee David Klein, Esq., Referee  11 Market Street  Poughkeepsie, NY 12601  (845) 454-9200   Locations of Property to be foreclosed:  Town of Beekman and Town of LaGrange, both Towns being in the County of Dutchess, State of New York, as more fully de- scribed above   DATED:  February 24, 2014                                 3450
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3561095">
  <start-date>2014-02-17</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-09</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    NOTICE OF SALE     SUPREME COURT OF THE STATE OF NEW YORK  COUNTY OF DUTCHESS  &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;- &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;- &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;X  CLARA A. TOOKER and KENNETH TOOKER,  Plaintiffs,   -against-   INDEX NO. 2013/3772  JAMES A. BOUFFARD, LOURENE R. BOUFFARD,  TD BANK, N.A., Succes- sor by Merger to Hud- son United  Bank, ARROW FINAN- CIAL SERVICES, LLC A/P/O  CITIBANK,  Defendants.  &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;- &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;- &mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;X   Attorney for Plaintiff: Fred W. Schaeffer, Esq., 12 Raymond Avenue, Poughkeepsie, New York   12603   (845) 454- 1190   Pursuant to a judgment of foreclosure and sale duly dated January 13, 2014, I the undersigned Referee will sell at pub- lic auction at DUTCHESS COUNTY COURTHOUSE, 10 MARKET STREET, POUGHKEEPSIE, NEW YORK 12601 ON MARCH 19th ,  2014 at 10:30 a.m. premises known as 29 Johnson Road, LaGrang- eville, New York 12540.   ALL that certain plot, piece or parcel of land, with the buildings and improvements thereon erected, situate, lying and being in the Town of LaGrange, County of Dutchess and State of New York, being more particularly known and designated as Lot No. 32 on a certain map en- titled &ldquo;Map of Grand- view Estates&ldquo;, which map was filed in the Of- fice of the Clerk of the County of Dutchess on October 19, 1964 as Map No. 3264.   Approximate amount of lien $169,424.02 plus in- terest and costs.   Premises will be sold subject to provisions of filed Judgment Index #2013/3772.   Michael D. Kranis, Esq., Referee  40 Garden Street  Poughkeepsie, NY 12601   Dated:February 11, 2014                                     1095
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564557">
  <start-date>2014-03-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-02</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    NOTICE    PLEASE TAKE NOTICE that the Town Board of the Town of Fishkill will hold a Public Hearing on Wednesday, March 19, 2014, at 7:00pm; or as soon thereafter as possible, at Town Hall, 807 Route 52, Fishkill, New York; introducing Local Law #1 of 2014 to Amend Chapter 150 en- titled &ldquo;Zoning&ldquo; of the Code of the Town of Fishkill and the Zoning Map of the Town of Fishkill in order to re- zone a 21.1 parcel made up of five separate tax lots form the residential 15 (R15) Zoning District to the Restricted Busi- ness (RB) Zoning Dis- trict .    TAKE FURTHER NO- TICE, that copies of the aforesaid proposed lo- cal law will be available for examination at the office of the Clerk of the Town of Fishkill, at the Town Hall, 807 Route 52, Fishkill, New York, between the hours of 8:00 am through 3:00pm on Monday - Friday be- tween the date of this notice and the date of the public hearing.   TAKE FURTHER NO- TICE, that all persons interested and citizens shall have an opportuni- ty to be heard on said proposal at that time and place aforesaid.    By: Darlene Bellis  Town Clerk    Dated: February 27, 2014   Fishkill Town Hall                                   4557
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563379">
  <start-date>2014-03-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-02</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    NOTICE TO BIDDERS  The Board of Education of the Red Hook Central School District, Red Hook, New York, re- quests sealed bids for:  ATHLETIC FIELD TURF MANAGEMENT  FOR THE 2014-2015 SCHOOL YEAR  Copies of specifications and bid forms may be obtained at the Admi- nistration Office  9 Mill Road, Red Hook, New York, during the hours of 9:00 a.m. to 12:00 noon and 1:00 p.m. to 3:00 p.m., Mon- day through Friday (e- xcluding holidays).  All bids are to be re- turned as indicated on the Instruction to Bid- ders by:  Monday, March 31, 2014 at 2:00PM__at which time all bids will be opened publicly.  Bids received after the specified time will be rejected and re- turned unopened.  The Board of Education reserves the right to re- ject any and all bids and re-advertise.  Elena Maskell  District Clerk                                 3379
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564353">
  <start-date>2014-03-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-02</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    PUBLIC NOTICE   NOTICE IS HEREBY GIVEN, that Requests for Proposals for 2014 Recreation Bus Service for the Town of Dover should be submitted to the Town Clerk of the Town of Dover. All par- ties interested in sub- mitting proposals can pick up a proposal with instructions and terms starting Wednesday, March 5, 2014 from the Town Clerk's Office, during normal business hours between 8:30 a.m. and 4:00 p.m., Monday through Friday   All proposals must be submitted to the Town Clerk of the Town of Dover at Town Hall, 126 East Duncan Hill Road, Dover Plains, New York 12522 no later than 10:00 a.m. on Wednes- day, March 19, 2014 when they will be opened and publicly read.   The Town of Dover re- serves the right to re- ject any and all propos- als or to accept the pro- posal which it deems most favorable to the interests of the Town of Dover.   Dated:   March 5, 2014    Dover Plains, New York    BY ORDER OF THE TOWN BOARD    Katie Palmer- House Town Clerk  126 East Duncan Hill Road  Dover Plains, New York                                     4353
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564662">
  <start-date>2014-03-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-04</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    PUBLIC NOTICES  PLEASE TAKE NOTICE, that the Village of Mil- lbrook has filed as of February 27, 2014, the Annual Financial Report for the fiscal year 2012- 2013 with the Office of the State Comptroller. A review copy is avail- able in the Village Clerk's Office during normal business hours.  Dated: February 28, 2014  Linda T. Wiltse  Clerk/Treasurer                                  4662
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3560944">
  <start-date>2014-03-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-18</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    REFEREE'S NOTICE OF SALE IN FORECLOSURE   STATE OF NEW YORK  SUPREME COURT- COUNTY OF DUTCHESS  HSBC BANK USA, N.A., Plaintiff against JOHN SPADAFORA, et al. De- fendants. Pursuant to a judgment of foreclosure and sale executed by the Honorable Christine A. Sproat, J.S.C., on No- vember 1, 2013, and filed with the Dutchess County Clerk on No- vember 8, 2013, I, the undersigned Referee will sell at public auc- tion at the Dutchess County Courthouse, 1st Floor rear vestibule, 10 Market Street, in the City of Poughkeepsie, Dutchess County, New York on 3/28/14 at 10:00 a.m. Premises common- ly known as 611 Route 376, East Fishkill, NY 12533. ALL that tract or parcel of land, situate and being in the Town of East Fishkill, County of Dutchess and State of New York. Section: 6457 Block: 01 Lot: 64936.  Approximate amount of lien $263,302.93 plus inter- est and costs. Premises will be sold subject to provisions of filed Judgment Index #2013- 259.   Dated:  February 10, 2014  THEONI STAMOS- SALOTTO, Esq., Referee    Jonathan D. Pincus, At- torney at Law  Attorney for Plaintiff  1387 Fairport Road, Bldg. 700, Suite 710  Fairport, NY  14450  Telephone: 585-256- 8000                                     0944
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564355">
  <start-date>2014-03-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-02</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>2000</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    TOWN OF DOVER  NOTICE OF 2014 MOW- ING & TRIMMING  INVITATION FOR BID   The Town of Dover is seeking a single vendor to provide for mowing and trimming services for various Town prop- erties.  Bids must in- clude the cost of a con- tract from April 1, 2014 through November 15, 2014 (weather permit- ting) for weekly mow- ing and trimming serv- ices for the following Town properties:   J.H. Ketcham Memorial Pool  J.H. Ketcham Pavilion area  Palmer's Field   Tabor Wing House   American Legion Me- morial Grounds   Dover Veteran's Memorial Library   Dover Town Hall and Transfer Station  Thomas J. Boyce Park  Stone Church Mowing Area  J. H. Ketcham Hose Company Stations# 1 and # 2.   Complete bid specifica- tions are available starting Wednesday, March 5, 2014 from the Town Clerk's Office dur- ing regular business hours:  Monday through Friday, 8:00 a.m. to 4:00 p.m.  Checks should be made payable to the Town of Dover.  Bids are to be submitted no later than 10:00 a.m. on Wednesday , March 19, 2014 to the office of the Town Clerk, Town of Dover, 126 East Duncan Hill Road, Dover Plains, NY  12522, and must be accompanied by a re- fundable bid bond in the amount of $500.00 made payable to the Town of Dover. Bids must be in the actual possession of the Town Clerk at or prior to the exact time indicated above.  Bids received by the correct time and date will be opened and publicly read.  Bids must be submitted in a sealed envelope prop- erly addressed to the Town of Dover, Town Clerk and must be clearly marked as fol- lows:   PROPOSAL FOR MOW- ING AND TRIMMING BID 2014  10:00 a.m. March 19, 2014.   Facsimile submissions will not be accepted. The Town will not be re- sponsible for late rec- eipt of improperly ad- dressed envelopes.  The Town reserves the right to accept or reject any bid or any part thereof, unless otherwise speci- fied, and to waive any minor informality in any bid, deemed by the Town to be in the best interests of the Town.   All information and bids submitted by bidders will be made available for public inspection following award, except to the extent the bidder designates, and the Town of Dover concurs that trade secrets or other proprietary data contained in the bid documents remain con- fidential.  If a bidder designates a portion of its bid as confidential, bidder shall isolate and identify in writing the confidential portion(s) at the time of submis- sion.  Any questions re- lated to this invitation to bid shall be directed to Teri Ptasnick, Recre- ation Director (phone: 845-832-9168).   By Order of The  Dover Town Board  Katie Palmer-House, Town Clerk                                  4355
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562148">
  <start-date>2014-02-19</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-04-12</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3120</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    MILLBROOK Condo 2br,2ba,gar 53 Bennett Com, Exc Con- d-Nice View PriceTo- Sell 175,000 Lsnyd@o- ptonline.net 631-793-2092
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562012">
  <start-date>2014-02-14</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-14</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3123</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    WAPPINGERS FALLS Modern Mobile home, 3BR, Washer/ Dryer, Deck. Behind Galleria. Small Dogs allowed. New Roof & Carpeting. Lot Rent: $535/mo. $19,950. Owner financ- ing. 845-266-8261
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562219">
  <start-date>2014-02-19</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-15</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3131</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    LaGrange Professional Building: Rt 55 & Bush- wick Rd. 1200 sq ft, for- mer DR office with exam & reception area. Ample parking, $1700/mo. + Utils. Call Jeff 914-204-2282 Call Bill at 845-795-1990
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564690">
  <start-date>2014-03-01</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-28</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3183</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    BEACON 3BR, Or four, option fur- nished, 1.5BA, LR, fam. rm,, dishwasher, wash- er / dryer, deck,  patio, walk to train+ stores. $1600 + utils. or option to buy neg. Parking. 70 mins NYC. 845-440-3345
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3560844">
  <start-date>2014-02-08</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-07</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3183</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    Pleasant Valley 3BR, 1BA, Country Set- ting, hdwd floors, Lg. Master walk-in closet. No smoking/dogs, $1400/mo. + Utils & Security. 845-325-2805
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564409">
  <start-date>2014-02-28</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-14</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3183</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK/C 2BR, 1BA House, enclosed porch, yard, basement. No smoking, $1300/mo. + Utilities & Security. 518-421-1462
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3561864">
  <start-date>2014-02-13</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-14</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3206</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    MILTON: 4BR, 2.5BA well-maintained home. Centrally located. 3.5 mi. south of MH Bridge; 10 mi. north of New- bugh-Beacon Bridge. Just off Rte 9W in a safe area. Granite counter tops, dish- washer, garden tub, patio, fireplace, C/air. Small pets allowed. $2250/month + utili- ties. Avail. 4/1. Call (845)795-5400.
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562120">
  <start-date>2014-02-15</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-14</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3210</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    DOVER PLAINS 14x70 3BR, pvt property, $850/month + utilities. Security required. No pets/smoking. Call (845) 325-3828
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563059">
  <start-date>2014-02-20</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-21</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    E. Fishkill/Hopewell 1BR apt, $875/month. includes Heat & Elec. near IBM and shop- ping. Extra Storage. Sec & Refs required. No pets or smoking. 845-635-3375
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562314">
  <start-date>2014-02-20</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-21</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    HYDE PARK Nice Studio Apt. $650. <U>FREE UTILITIES!</U> No pets.  1 mo sec. Background check.  845-849-5102
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564616">
  <start-date>2014-03-01</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-28</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    HYDE PARK Spring Sale! FIRST MONTH FREE WITH ONE YEAR LEASE. 1BR apt, $900 includes all utilities. 1.5 month security. 845-225-0875
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564621">
  <start-date>2014-03-01</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-28</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    HYDE PARK Spring Sale! FIRST MONTH FREE WITH ONE YEAR LEASE. 2BR apt, $1075 includes all utilities. 1.5 month security. 845-225-0875
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3560891">
  <start-date>2014-02-08</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-07</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    LAGRANGEVILLE Arlington Schools. 2BR,  1 Bath, LR, wash/dry.$1100/mo. Ht/HW  incl'd. 1 mo.rent/1 mo. Sec. & Ref's.347-236-1983
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3559757">
  <start-date>2014-02-05</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-03</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    Marlboro 2BR Beautiful large 2BR, DR, Kitchen, LR, & 2 full Bathrooms. $1125/mo. includes Heat, wall to wall carpet.  Nice, quiet area. Rich 845-236-9219
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562350">
  <start-date>2014-02-26</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-22</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    PINE PLAINS 2BR. Lake view. $895/ month, Heat & Hot Water Included. 1 month rent + security required. Available immediately. Call (914)664-7559
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3559575">
  <start-date>2014-02-01</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-04-04</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    PLEASANT VALLEY: Brookside Meadows 1, 2 & 3 Bedroom Luxury Apartments. New Construction  Town Homes and Apartments available Now! Call (845) 635-2600 brooksidemeadows.com
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563421">
  <start-date>2014-02-26</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-22</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK/C 2BR apt., 162 Parker Ave. $1100/mo. includes Ht/HW. Big backyard. Off-st Parking. No pets 1.5 mos. Sec req'd. 845-473-2644
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3560850">
  <start-date>2014-02-08</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-07</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK/C CLEAN/QUIET, 1BR + den/home office. hardwood floors, Off-Street parking. $750/mo.  Call 845-452-4351.
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3560997">
  <start-date>2014-02-12</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-08</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK/C:  Newly renovated 3BR, $1200/mo. + utils. In- cludes garage. Section 8 OK. Avail Now. Nice Apt - must see! Near Walkway Over the Hudson. Off- street parking. Call Ken- ny, 914-497-3882
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564303">
  <start-date>2014-02-27</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-28</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK/C Smith St. near Morgan Lake. Newly renovated 3BR apt., in 2 Family house. $1000/mo. + Utils. off-st-pkng.  Private backyard. Call 914-489-9822
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563534">
  <start-date>2014-03-01</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-30</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK KAAL ROCK Manor Apartments Luxury Studio $690; 1BR's starting at $865; 2 BR starting at $925; 2BR Townhouses starting at $1250; 3BR  Townhouses starting at $1420. 1 year lease avail- able. Includes: Heat, hot water, wall to wall carpet, Air con- ditioning, dishwash- er,  Kenmore appli- ances. Night Securi- ty on staff. No pets. Country setting, some apartments have  river view. A warm & friendly  atmosphere. Tennis court, pool, all  private entrances. Commuter bus & Metro North Rail- road within walking distance. 845-471-1890
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563533">
  <start-date>2014-02-26</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-28</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK/T: Bright & clean 2BR 1st floor apt. private car port, washer & dryer, deck,  $1100/month + utils. Avail. 3/1/2014. (845)440-6691, lve msg
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563543">
  <start-date>2014-02-27</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-14</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK/T Cherry Hill Large 1BR, 2 large walk in closets, deck, Ht/HW included. $950/mo.  1 mo. sec. No pets. 845-981-9003
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3561993">
  <start-date>2014-02-14</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-30</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK/T Cherry Hill West Newly renovated 2BR Duplexes. Washer/ Dryer Hookups. $1250/mo. Call 845-485-4412
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563334">
  <start-date>2014-02-22</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-30</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK/T: Lge 1BR, dish- washer, EiK, patio. $800 + utils. 845-463-1536
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3560901">
  <start-date>2014-02-08</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-04-04</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    Pok/Town  Dutchess Apts  Arlington area, Luxury 1BR & 2BR, Ht/HW incl. $1020-$1200/mo. A/C, Pool, Appliances  845 454-4878 Hours: M-F, 9am-8pm Sat & Sun 10am-3pm  www.hubrealty.com
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3560900">
  <start-date>2014-02-08</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-04-04</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    Pok/Town Ridgefield Apts  Luxury1BR and 2BR . $995-$1275/mo. Ht&HW included  New Kitchen & Bath w/Granite. 845 454-2290 Hours: M-F, 9am-8pm Sat & Sun, 10am-3pm  www.hubrealty.com
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3561994">
  <start-date>2014-02-14</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-14</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    Rhinebeck/Clinton One mile TSP, five miles Rhinebeck, 1BR, suit- able for one, incl Ht/HW & Elec. No smoking / pets. $750 / month. 845-266-4387
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564687">
  <start-date>2014-03-01</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-28</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    STANFORDVILLE 1BR + office located on 8 acres. Beautiful country setting, very private. No dogs/smoking. $795/month+ utils. (845) 876-1151
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562013">
  <start-date>2014-02-14</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-14</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    WAPPINGERS FALLS Modern Mobile home, 3BR, Washer/Dryer, behind Galleria. No Dogs. $1035/mo. (845)266-8261
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564624">
  <start-date>2014-03-01</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-14</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3218</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    WAPPINGERS Studio, $695/mo. HT/HW incl'd. Freshly Painted, New carpet & New Appliances. Off-st Pkng. Some pets ok. Call 845-463-2614
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563314">
  <start-date>2014-02-22</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-26</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3307</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    Highland-Duplex  -Newly renovated 2BR, + sm office, lg yard, covered deck off kit.No pets, Smoke & drug free, 3 mi Bridge & Thruway. Ref's,credit chk, 1st, last + 1mo. sec req'd. $1500 incl. Ht/HW. 845-691-2021.
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563294">
  <start-date>2014-02-22</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-21</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3307</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    HIGHLAND  Large 1BR, 1st floor end unit. Parking next to unit. On-site laundry. Private/Quiet neigh- borhood. Next to Lloyd Town Hall. Near Rt 9W. Mins. to Pok bridge, Metro North, Rt 9 & hospitals. $925/mo. Ht/HW included. 1 mo. security. 845-391-3747
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3560754">
  <start-date>2014-02-07</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-07</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3307</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    MILTON Beautiful, new manufac- tured home. 2BR, 2 full baths. Choice lot. All new furniture. Small, quiet country setting. Ideal location. $925 / month. No pets. Call 845-616-4919/845-795- 6104; 1-941-639-2220
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562360">
  <start-date>2014-02-20</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-30</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3330</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    BEACON: Nice area, close to downtown, I- 84 & train station, Pri- vate parking. Free ca- ble.  845-831-8360
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564688">
  <start-date>2014-03-01</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-28</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3330</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    MILAN/RED HOOK: Rooms w/pvt BA. Utils incl. Free WiFi. No smoking / pets. Close to TSP. Located in Milan near Red Hook, Rhinebeck, Pine Plains. Starting at $150/week.  For appt, (845)876-1151
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3562270">
  <start-date>2014-02-19</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-15</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3330</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    POK- Rooms avail now! $150/week including  Utilities and Cable. Share Kitchen/Bath. No smoking/pets. Two Weeks Security Required. Call 845-235-5360
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3563279">
  <start-date>2014-02-23</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-30</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3330</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    Wappingers StoneGate Nice furnished rooms. Rte 9. Private bath, internet, TV, refrigera- tor. 845-297-3149 or 914-474-5176
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3564566">
  <start-date>2014-02-28</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-03-30</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>3445</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    WE BUY JUNK CARS  Used parts & tires sold. ID#7087068 Greens 724-5362 or 724-3928
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

<ad id="3553777">
  <start-date>2014-01-03</start-date>
  <end-date>2014-04-02</end-date>
  <placement>General</placement>
  <position>6072</position>
  <ad-text><![CDATA[
    ROOFING PLUS 452-5981 / 309-4411
  ]]></ad-text>
</ad>

</dcd>
